"lang"
{
	"Language"		"English"
	"Tokens"
	{		
		"addon_game_name"							"Dota Fusions"
		"popup_title"								"Welcome To Dota Fusions"
		"popup_body"								"In this game mode, you can combine the abilities of two heroes into one.\n\nThe fused hero will have the appearance and attributes of a primary hero, and is able to equip any abilities from either heroes.\n\nSwapping abilities can be done whenever you are near a fountain through the fusion ability tab.\n\nFirst, select your fusion hero, and then your primary hero."
		"fusion_hero_title_label"					"Fusion Hero"
		"primary_hero_title_label"					"Primary Hero"
	}
}
